cwbz.com 2011-09-25

# Privacy Policy

**Information we collect**

Cwbz is dedicated to providing services in entertaining and educational spheres. Our Online Privacy Policy is committed to protect the privacy of our users online and is also targeted at maintaining compliance of users with our rules and delivering better service to our customers. We may request some personal information in case you would like to subscribe to a free newsletter in order to receive notifications regarding games located on our web-site. All the personal information that we collect is given on a voluntary basis by the user and includes your name, e-mail, year of birth and gender. In case the user is under 13 we strongly recommend to have the parents' agreement in order to subscribe to the newsletter or carry out other online activities. For safety and security purposes the system automatically registers your IP and the country of staying. 

**How we use the information**

Only with your permission Cwbz might contact you by the submitted e-mail to inform about special offers and the games released to keep you updated about our production. We may sometimes use non-personable anonymous data for analytical and statistical purposes. Information of this kind helps us to work out the design and content of our site and make the experience of our customers more pleasant and convenient.

Communication on Cwbz

As an addition Cwbz offers our visitors an opportunity of realizing communication with other online game players through our chat. Even though we use all the possible means to filter the obscene words in our chat but we still point out that every user should understand the importance of using of proper and decent vocabulary while navigating our site. Cwbz is neither responsible for the content of conversations carrying out via our chat, nor for the consequences of sharing of personal information with other guests. In case you happen to be severely offended by the expressions of other visitors please feel free to contact the administration of Cwbz by submitting a comment to support service. We do need to have your e-mail in case you experience any kind of technical problems using our products and make a request for our assistance through the support system. In such case your e-mail is used by our employees as a mean of communication with the customers and as a mean of informing you about the recommendable possible solution of the problem. 

**Linking to third party sites**

To provide information not available on our site, Cwbz may locate links to third party web-sites. It is strongly recommendable to get acquainted with online privacy policies of third party sites before submitting any personal information requested as their rules might be different from our policy. Downloading and installing of Exe files that belong to third party sites should be done only at your own risk as they might be containing unexpected threats. Cwbz is not responsible for the content and danger that might emerge visiting third party sites. 

**Third-party advertising companies**

We broadcast advertisements to out visitors that is accomplished by third-party advertising companies. Any questions or problems appearing out of the advertisements should be directed to them. Advertising companies may be using generalized non-personable information about our customers' visits to our web-site to offer their services and products that might interest you. Cwbz is not responsible for the content of commercials and their possible effect on the customers. Any concerns about publicity located on the web-site should be clarified by making direct requests to advertisers. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Later on there are possibilities of appearing of new terms and regulations concerning access to the web-site, our products and services, and their further usage by the visitors. Cwbz has a unique right to introduce new rules to our Privacy Policy and correct the old one's whenever we consider it necessary. 

**Contact us**

In case of having any questions about this Privacy Policy, the services and products we offer on our web-site, or in case of appearing of any technical problem connected with the functioning of the site, please do not hesitate to contact us by sending your comment, question or opinion to the administration. We are always glad to render assistance in any technical problem, find out about your point of view concerning our products or answer your question. All suggestions, feedback and partnership offers are welcome.
